onlinefreelogo.com 2016-06-24

# Online Logo Design Website | Our Privacy Policy – Online Free Logo

Our Privacy Policy is designed to protect and keep confidential your personal information. This document explains the process for collating and restricted dissemination of information we collect from you. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information about you collected by our affiliates or third party websites that may post links or advertisements on or otherwise be accessible from the Site. The information collected by these affiliates or third party websites is subject to their own privacy policies. By using this Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this Privacy Policy. From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to check back and review this Privacy Policy so that you may always know what personally identifiable information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of this Site will be subject to the then current Privacy Policy. 

Your IP address, browser details, OS etc are automatically collected when you visit our site or when you are a member with us. Such information gathering helps us in administering our Site and diagnosing problems with our server. Also, we track your browsing activities on our Site and the links or sites you visit before and after our Site. This helps us to do internal research on your interests and liking and serve you better in the future. 

When you send us information through e-mails or by filling out a form and give us information while registering for an account with us, we collect those information about you. For example- when you register for an account with us or when you participate in any competition organized by onlinefreelogo.com you give us details like your name, email address, billing address, password etc. This may also include personal information such as gender, marital status, age, financial status etc. 

In addition to above mentioned information, we collect history of your orders, payments and purchases with us and your billing history. 

Email communications, blogs, chat room discussions, board communication, instant messages, fax communication etc all this is stored with us. 

Our Site uses 'cookies' and other server logs to gather information about your activities on our Site. Using these, we are enabled to recall you as a customer/ visitor and also your orders or preferences with the help of records of your earlier visits. Through cookies, we can then tailor our Site elements and special offers to you. This helps us to gather feedback in order to constantly improve the Site and serve you better. You can always reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to display a message when a cookie is being sent. If you reset your browser, some of this Site features and functionality will not be available to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies and similar files by onlinefreelogo.com only and does not cover the use of cookies and similar files by any third party advertisers or websites linked to the Site. 

Your personal information is collected for purpose of maintaining, improving, administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may use the information collected to notify you about important changes to the Site and new services and special offers that we feel you will find valuable. If you do not wish to receive such communication, you may notify us at any time, or unsubscribe for the same. We may also share the personal information we collect with other companies with whom we have business, marketing arrangements. We may also disclose information, including personal information; we collect about you in other circumstances as required or permitted by law. For example, onlinefreelogo.com reserves the right to disclose personal information, including account information, when we believe such disclosure is appropriate to cooperate with an investigation of activities claimed to be unlawful, to enforce our terms of use or to protect the rights or property of onlinefreelogo.com or others. When you use certain services that are to an open, public environment or forum including (without limitation) any blog, community or discussion board, it is not confidential and does not constitute personal information, and is not subject to protection under our Privacy Policy. 

In order to carry out certain business functions, such as order fulfillment, e-mail delivery, marketing, or for payments that you make to onlinefreelogo.com for any purchase, we sometime hire other companies to perform such services on our behalf. We may disclose personal information that we collect about you to these companies to enable them to perform these services, but they are required to safeguard the personal information and are not authorized to use it for any purpose other than completing their contractual requirements to offer us their services. You acknowledge and agree that in the interests of improving personalization and service efficiency, we may, under controlled and secure circumstances, share your personal information with our affiliates. 

While visiting our Site, you may be presented with links to other websites and opportunity to purchase third party products or services. If you click on one of the presented offers, you will be redirected to the site of the third party, and any information you provide in response to the offer will be collected and used by the third party and not by onlinefreelogo.com. Information you provide to the third party and any dealings you have with the third party will be governed by the privacy and other policies of that third party. We will have no liability, whatsoever in that connection. 

For promotion of onlinefreelogo.com we may send offers through emails, sms and physical mailers. You have the option to subscribe/ unsubscribe to communication from onlinefreelogo.com. This option is available when you are registering with us. Also, you can drop in a mail or call our helpdesk for the same facility. Your account too will have the option to unsubscribe the newsletters or any communication from onlinefreelogo.com or some other third parties. 

We have reasonable safeguarding techniques to help us protect your nonpublic personal information against loss, misuse, disclosure and alteration. For example, we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt your credit card information when you purchase products through our Site. When you establish an account at onlinefreelogo.com you choose a password to help protect your account information. 

This Privacy Policy was last modified on (date). onlinefreelogo.com holds the right to revise this Privacy Policy from time to time and we will post a revised Privacy Policy on our Site. Any revision will be posted on this Site, and shall be effective as of date
